(Sheldon:)Where am I going to find
uranium-235 this time of night?
(Sheldon:)Come on, CraigsList.
(Leonard:)Is it racist that I took you
to an Indian restaurant?
(Priya:)It's okay, I like Indian food.
(Leonard:)Or as you probably call it
back home, "food." (chuckles)
(Priya:)Why didn't you wear
your contacts?
(Priya:)Don't you like them?
(Leonard:)No, no, I do.
(Leonard:)It's just I knew I was having
curry tonight
(Leonard:)and I only want one part
of my body to burn at a time.
You know... (clears throat)
(Priya:)...my company offered me a
position here in Los Angeles.
(Leonard:)Does that mean you'd relocate
here permanently?
(Priya:)Maybe. What do you think?
(Leonard:)I love it.
(Leonard:)That's great!
(knocking)
(Penny(knocking on window):)Hi!
(Penny(knocking on window):)Hi! Just hang on.